A Guide to the Directors' Correspondence of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1933-1977 (bulk 1934-1976)
Library of Virginia
- Chamber Music Society: Sub-Committee Meeting, 1957 November 25 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Dance Society: Sub-Committee Meeting, 1957 November 11 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Development Committee: Meeting 1957 November 26 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Entertainment Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Entertainment Committee: Meeting 1957 October 21 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Events, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Events: Barton, Mr and Mrs. - Party, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Events: Butzner Dinner, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Events: Christmas Party, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Events: Christmas Preparations 1957, 1956-1957 (Box 90, Folder 15)
- Events: College Drama Festival,, 1956-1957 (Box 90, Folder 16)
- Events: Council Lecture - Luncheon, 1962-1965 (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Events: DeJarnette Luncheon, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 18)
- Events: Jenkins, Alfred Peyton - Party, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 19)
- Events: Junior League Luncheon, 1961-1967 (Box 90, Folder 20)
- Events: National Secretaries Association Tea, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 21)
- Events: Trustee Dinner, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 22)
- Events: Tuckahoe Garden Club Tea, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 23)
- Events: United Daughters of the Confederacy Tea, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 24)
- Executive Committee: Minutes 1957 January 9 (Box 90, Folder 25)
- Executive Committee: Minutes 1957 February 12 (Box 90, Folder 26)
- Executive Committee: Minutes 1957 March 19 (Box 90, Folder 27)
- Executive Commitee: Minutes 1957 May 10 (Box 90, Folder 28)
- Executive Committee: 1957 September 9 (Box 90, Folder 29)
- Executive Committee: Minutes 1957 November 22 (Box 90, Folder 30)
- Exhibitions: Virginia Artists 1957, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 31)
- Fellowship Committee: Meeting 1957 May 11 (Box 90, Folder 32)
- Governor's Conference (1957), 1956-1957 (Box 90, Folder 33)
- Honors and Awards Committee, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 34)
- Membership Committee: Meeting 1957 October 29 (Box 90, Folder 35)
- Naval Review (June 12, 1957), 1957 (Box 90, Folder 36)
- Theatre Advisory Committee 1957 September 20 (Box 90, Folder 37)
- Theatre Committee: Meeting 1957 October 4 (Box 90, Folder 38)
- Theatre Committee: Meeting 1957 November 7 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Travel: Williamsburg, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee 1957 February 26 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee 1957 March 18 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee 1957 October 14 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee 1957 December 7 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: Minutes 1957 January 9 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: Minutes 1957 February 12 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: Minutes 1957 March 19 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: Minutes 1957 November 22 (Box 91, Folder 8)